https://www.nicoladexter.com/privacy-notice/

Call: 07711462923
MENUMENUMENUMENUHomeProblems treatedTherapies available
Hypnosis/hypnotherapyNLPTime Line TherapyCoaching Program
More
TestimonialsQualifications and insuranceFAQTerms and conditionsPrivacy NoticeDisclaimer
Contact
Privacy Notice
This privacy notice governs the manner in which Nicola Dexter collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this website.  This privacy notice applies to this site, all other sites and all products and services provided by Nicola Dexter.
Personal identification information may be collected in a variety of ways, including visiting this site or others linked with Nicola Dexter, registering on any of the sites, filling in any forms or in any other way connected with Nicola Dexter providing her professional services or information.
This site may use “cookies” to enhance user experience.  The user’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them.  A user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies or to send an alert when cookies are being sent.
How Collected Information Is Used:-
To respond to requests from the user
To send “requested for” information to the user
To be included in the therapeutic services Nicola Dexter offers
If any information is sent via a subscribed service, there is a detailed unsubscribe instruction on how to unsubscribe
How your information is protected
Nicola Dexter adopts appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on the site
Sharing your personal information
Nicola Dexter may share your information with her colleagues with your permission in order to provide an enhanced service.
Nicola Dexter does not sell, trade or rent users personal identification information to others.
£400 (if paid in advance)
